technoxyz.com 2019-04-02

# Privacy Policy - Technoxyz.Com

**What Information do we store?**

Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of Technoxyz.com. We, hereby state that we won’t sell, share or provide your email ID to any 3rd party services. All the information will be solely kept with Technoxyz and will only be used for sending weekly newsletters or promoting services.

 **Cookies**

A ‘Cookie’ is a ‘Non-Personal Information’ that is not personally identifiable to you and that we automatically collect when you access our website with a web browser. It is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows Technoxyz.com to recognize you each time you visit or login to this site. Technoxyz does not use cookies to store visitor’s information. Third party services such as Google Adsense and Google Analytics store cookies to track visitors and for better ad management. For any concern with a third party, please contact them directly.

 **External Links**

Technoxyz does provide links to other websites that are not under our direct control. Once you have left Technoxyz and landed on another site, then it’s their privacy policy that comes into action. We won’t be able to control a user’s privacy on another site. We cannot also be held liable/accountable for any loss/damage occurring as a result of activity on another website.

 **Affiliates**

Technoxyz uses Amazon associates program for promoting products from Amazon through affiliate links. Whenever a user buys a product from those links, we earn commission. However, we only recommend relevant products that have high ratings and positive reviews.

 **Privacy Policy Updates**

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time. You should review this Privacy Policy frequently.

 **Questions About  Privacy Policy and Disclaimer**

If you have any questions about our privacy practices or this policy, please contact us.
